是时候感受一下飞速滑行的感觉了
It's time to ride the slide and taste the wind.
汉弗莱  你真是个天才
Humphrey, you are totally genius.
快点  要出发啦
Come on. Let's do it.
风之狼
Air wolf!
同志们  同志们
Guys. Guys.
我们还在原地呢
We're not moving!
这驯鹿是我的了
This caribou is mine.
凯特  人家不是驯鹿  我可是你妹妹
Kate, I'm not a caribou. I'm your sister!
抓住你了
Gotcha.
欧米加可不玩这些
Omegas don't play like this.
没人能逃出史上最强大的阿尔法之手
You can't escape the greatest Alpha ever.
是嘛  我刚不就逃脱了
Well, I just did.
我们要完蛋了
We're going to die!
保持平衡  控制好
Keep it steady! Keep it steady!
我刚刚大脑短路了吗
What was I thinking?
棒极了
That was great!
同志们  今天我们成功飞天了
We are flying today, guys.
汉弗莱  怎么是你
Humphrey?
凯特  是你啊
Kate?
你在这里干嘛呢
What are you doing up here?
我在练习捕猎午餐呢
I'm practice hunting for our lunch.
正好  我快要把我的午餐吐出来了
Good, 'cause I'm about to lose mine.
是吗
You are?
我会努力咽下去的
I'll try to swallow it.
凯特
Kate!
是时候回去了
It's time to go.
就来  老爸
I'm coming, Dad.
你去哪儿
Where're you going?
阿尔法学校  要上到春季呢
Alpha school. It goes till spring.
春季吗
Spring?
但还有一整个冬天没过呢
But that's a whole winter away.
汉弗莱  我知道你是凯特的朋友
I know you're Kate's friend, Humphrey.
但到了下个春季  她将是位受训的阿尔法
But by next spring, she will be a trained Alpha,
是整个群体的首领
the future leader of the pack.
毫无疑问你将是个聪明的欧米加
No doubt you'll be a clever Omega.
学着保持距离
Learn to keep the peace.
并且  汉弗莱
And Humphrey,
要记得提醒大家享受生活啊
remind us all to have fun.
可是...  可是...
But... But...
阿尔法和欧米加不能...
Alphas and Omegas can't...
那话怎么说来着
How do you say it?
那是我们的习俗  狼群的法则
That's our custom. The law of the pack.
狼罗汉
Wolf pile!
幼稚的欧米加们
Silly Omegas.
阿尔法与欧米加
从林服务
锯齿公园  钓鱼和打猎
左转弯  三十度
Take a left! Thirty degrees!
小咸  起帆
Salty, give us some sail draft!
我觉得我感受到了风的气息
I think I taste the wind.
不对  是虫的味道
No, just a bug.
穆池  准备好  调低帆桁
Hey, Mooch, get ready! Lower the boom!
-好嘞  -抓紧了  同志们
- All right! - Hang on, boys!
伙计们  我们真得练练...  刹车
Guys, we really need to work on the... brakes!
-刹车?  -刹车?
- Brakes? - Brakes?
狼罗汉
Wolf pile!
把你的屁股从我脸前挪开
Get your butt out of my face.
我们撞到什么了
What did we hit?
春天
Spring.
看看是谁从阿尔法学校回来了
Look who's back from Alpha school.
别妄想吃天鹅肉了  汉弗莱
Forget about it, Humphrey.
凯特现在是阿尔法了
Kate's an Alpha now.
而你还是欧米加
And you're an Omega.
我们就是朋友
We're friends, okay?
没错  就朋友打住
Exactly. Just friends. End of story.
你最好把目光调向那边
You better set your sights over there.
莉芭和珍妮丝  素食狼
Reba and Janice, the vegetarians.
好吧
Okay.
看来今晚我们有驯鹿肉吃了  伙计们
Looks like we're eating caribou tonight, boys.
看  看
Hey. Hey.
东部狼群
Eastern Pack wolves.
小能  浩池  我们有伴儿了
Can-do, Hutch, we've got company.
这下好了  晚餐就这样跑掉了
Great. There goes dinner.
凯特也跑了
And there goes Kate.
-天哪  -驯鹿
- Holy... - Caribou!
散开
Scatter to the sides!
看这身手之敏捷
Look at those moves.
看领导我的
Settle the score, leader.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
-我还好  -你们到底什么毛病啊
- Yeah, I'm fine. - Hey, what's your problem,
你们这些东部蠢狗  那是我们的猎物
you stupid Eastern dog? That was our hunt.
你不能像那样冲出来打草惊蛇
You can't just snake it out from under us.
小能  退后
Can-do, back off.
你最好听她说的
You better listen to the girl.
松开  小能  浩池  散开
Hey, break it up. Can-do, Hutch, break it up!
好了  欧米加们  该我们出手了
All right, Omegas, duty calls.
住手小能  浩池  住手
Stop it. Can-do, Hutch, stop!
-喂  -甜心
- Hey! - Candy!
-凯特  -汉弗莱
- Kate. - Humphrey?
我还是轻饶不了这个龅牙傻瓜
I'm still going to tear this snaggletooth fool apart.
伙计们  调低帆桁
Guys, lower the boom!
汉弗莱  我们没时间找乐子
Humphrey, we don't have time for fun.
同志们  算了  别把皮毛弄褶了
Guys, guys, come on. Don't get your fur in a bunch.
你们这群狼给我们抹黑
You wolves are making us look bad.
连驯鹿都笑话我们
Come on, the caribou are laughing at us.
那要是月亮  我可连嗥叫都想省了
Now, that's a moon I don't want to howl to.
西部狼群  回你们地盘去
Western hunt group, get back to the den.
你们两个  回家去
The two of you, go home.
走啊
Now!
欧米加们  干的好
Omegas, good job.
这可好  我的首猎竟被我搞砸了
Great. My first hunt, and I blew it.
凯特  凯特  凯特
Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate, Kate.
别责备自己了  你刚才帅呆了
Don't beat yourself up. That's crazy. You were amazing.
我是说  如果饿了
I mean, if anyone's hungry,
我们还可以吃点...
they can eat...
他们可以吃...
They can always eat...
吃什么呢
What?
给
Here.
可以吃蓝莓
They can eat berries.
蓝莓非常有营养
Berries are really nutritious.
是吗  留着那话跟饥饿的狼群说去吧
Yeah. Tell that to a hungry pack.
东部狼群毁了凯特的狩猎
The Eastern Wolves ruined Kate's hunt.
幸运的是欧米加们在那里阻止了群架
Luckily, the Omegas were there to break up the fight.
-莉莉  -怎么啦
- Lilly. - What?
真有意思  别再玩你自己的尾巴了
Very funny. Stop playing with your tail.
凯特  怎么无精打采的
Kate, you're slouching.
这才对嘛
Thank you, honey.
你知道你看起来有多强壮和美丽吗
Do you see how strong and beautiful you are?
我的...
My...
任何食物都是恩赐  孩子
Any food is a blessing, dear.
温斯顿  过来和我们一起吃饭
Winston? Come join us for dinner?
速度
Now!
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, honey.
菜羹冷炙和骨头怎么能叫饭呢
Scraps and bones is no kind of dinner.
在我这里不行
Not for my pack.
对不起  父亲
I'm sorry, Dad.
那些东部狼群打乱了阵脚
It's just those Eastern Wolves.
不怪你  凯特
It's not your fault, Kate.
当他们闯入我们地盘时
When they crossed into our territory,
他们就破坏了群落守则
they broke pack law.
温斯顿
Winston.
小能被一群东部狼袭击了
Can-do was jumped by a group of Eastern Wolves.
这没什么大不了的
It ain't nothing.
快点  把他带进洞里来
Quickly, bring him into the den.
温斯顿  亲爱的  无论这是谁干的
Winston, honey, whoever did this,
我们都要让他好看
Let's rip his tail off and shove it down his throat.
老大  我们难道就要这样放任
Sir, are we just going to
他们破坏我们的捕猎吗
let them keep raiding our hunts
并且...
and...
让我们阿尔法族进入戒备状态
Put our Alphas on alert.
已经办好了  老大
Already done, sir.
好样的
Good job.
伙计们  说实话  驯鹿肉也没那么好吃
Guys, honestly, caribou is overrated.
相反现在应该想开点
Instead, now, keep an open mind,
我只希望你们也能接受其他的食物
I just want you to have an open mind here,
我们给你们带了蓝莓来
we bring you berries.
那松鼠怎么样呢
How about squirrels?
开玩笑的
Bad joke.
松鼠飞了
Flying squirrels.
温斯顿
Winston!
托尼  你看起来气色真好
Tony! You're looking good.
我后背僵得像块木头  椎间盘也裂开了
My back feels like wood. I got this disk that keeps cracking.
我都快被折磨疯了
Drives me crazy.
是啊  托尼  你就是只疯狂的狼
Yeah, Tony, you are one crazy wolf.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
就像你在我们捕猎过程中玩的跟踪把戏
Like that little game of tag during our hunt.
游戏还是让欧米加们去玩吧
Let's leave the playing to the Omegas.
你知道东部已经没有驯鹿可捕了
You know there's no caribou left in the east.
那是你的问题
You got a problem.
部群联盟  温斯顿  是你当初提议
Unite the packs, Winston. It was you who gave the big speech
让你女儿凯特和我儿子卡斯
that your daughter Kate and my son Garth
联姻以团结部群的
would marry and unite the packs.
卡斯知道他的使命  凯特知道吗
Garth knows his responsibility. Does Kate?
别担心  她知道的
Don't worry. She knows.
那就好
Good.
那她今晚可以在月圆狼嗥时跟卡斯见面
Then she can meet Garth tonight at the moonlight howl.
我不会让我的部群挨饿的  温斯顿
I won't let my pack starve, Winston.
非不得已之时  我们就爪牙相见吧
If we have to, we'll fight for the valley.
那肯定是个严重的错误
That would be a big mistake.
凯特  这个...
Kate. It's...
没关系  爸爸  我懂
It's okay, Dad. I understand.
这是...这是我的责任
It's... it's my responsibility.
伙伴们  我们得为月圆狼嚎做准备了
Guys, we got to get ready for the moonlight howl.
伙计们  有美眉哦
Guys, girls.
美眉啊
Girls?
你们很拉风啊
You are cool.
这样  让我打头阵...
So, let me go ahead...
让美眉们准备迎接你们  我们到时候见
prepare the girls for your arrival and you guys meet me there.
好戏要开始啦
Game on.
美眉
Girls.
凯特  你看着美极了
Kate, you look so beautiful.
如果卡斯越界了
Now, if Garth gets out of line,
就用你那美丽的獠牙
take those beautiful teeth of yours,
朝着他喉咙咬下去直到他一动不动为止
go for the throat, and don't let go until the body stops shaking.
如果我的小公主不想这么做
If my little girl doesn't want to do this,
如果她还没准备好...
if she's not ready...
放心  爸爸  我准备好了
Don't worry, Dad. I'm ready.
莉莉  快点
Come on, Lilly.
好了  好了
Okay. Okay.
你的皮毛看起来好极了
Your fur... it looks fantastic tonight.
-哦  上帝啊  -我得...
- Oh, my Gosh. - I had...
欧米加注意了
Omega alert.
我来搞定这个
I will handle this.
皮毛顺滑无比
It totally relaxes the knots.
你好
Hey.
我只有那一招
That's all I've got.
哇  一笑倾城啊
Wow. This is a new feeling.
伙计们  我全看见了
I saw the whole thing, guys.
我不敢相信她们竟然不睬你们
And, I cannot believe they didn't just fall all over you.
你说"你好"的时候我觉得你把握十足呢
When you yelled, ''Hey,'' I thought you cinched it right there.
你觉得你比我更有能耐吗
So, you think you can do better?
拜托
Please.
下个走上山坡的女孩  就是我的了
The next girl that comes up the hill, she's mine.
我从未见过如此美丽的她
I've never seen her look that good.
凯特真是漂亮极了
Kate is hot.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
站住
Hey.
你觉得你要去哪儿啊
Where do you think you're going?
汉弗莱  你知道规矩的
Humphrey, you know the rules.
你是不能和她共嗥的  她是阿尔法
You're not allowed to howl with her. She's an Alpha.
我们可以一起吃东西
We can eat together.
但我们不能  你知道  共嗥
But we can't, you know, howl together.
伙计们  我知道  我...我就是...
Guys, I know. I... I was just...
开玩笑
kidding.
别在意  兄弟  你还有我们呢
Cheer up, buddy. You still got us.
我们可是一辈子的朋友
Friends for life!
糟了
Ugly.
那你见过卡斯了吗
So, do you see Garth?
这下好了
Great.
我连他长什么样子都不知道
I'm not even sure what he looks like.
但我确信...
But I'm sure...
我们一眼就能认出他
we'll know him when we see him.
你好  凯特
Hey, Kate.
什么嘛
What?
卡斯
Garth.
莉莉  别碍事
Lilly, stand up.
卡斯  你好  很高兴见到你
Garth, hello. Good to see you.
-汉弗莱  -我的屁股  我的屁股
- Humphrey? - My butt! My butt.
真的很疼
It really hurts.
你真该治治你的咳嗽了
You should really do something about that cough.
小心  凯特  事情有些奇怪
Be careful, Kate. There's something going around.
尾巴和耳朵一日不如一日  真的
Tails and ears are falling off, literally.
我叫汉弗莱
Name's Humphrey.
卡斯
Garth.
哇  你很...你很大块头啊
Wow. You are a...you are a big one, aren't you?
你简直就是头驼鹿啊
Wow. You're practically a moose.
你把你的鹿角藏哪儿了
Where you hiding them antlers?
这小不点儿是谁
Who's the coyote?
小不点儿是谁?  我懂了
Who's the coyote? I get it.
很好  因为我是...
That's good, 'cause I'm, like...
一个无关紧要的人
No one important.
莉莉  你为何不带着小不点儿
Lilly, why don't you take little coyote
汉弗莱一边儿玩去呢
Humphrey and run along?
走吧  汉弗莱
Come on, Humphrey.
我们一起吃醋去吧
Let's go eat some of those bitter berries.
跟我说说你自己吧
So, tell me about yourself.
卡斯都喜欢干些什么呢
What does Garth like to do?
我很喜欢健身  你知道吗
Well, I'm really into fitness, you know?
短跑  伏地挺身
Rabbit sprints, tree squats.
你知道我们阿尔法必须保持身材来领导部群
You know us Alphas got to keep fit to lead the pack.
但真正让我着迷的是...
But, what really gets me going is...
你觉得怎么样啊
Was it good for you?
不可置信
Unbelievable.
你知道...
You know...
我只是...
I just...just...
稍等一下  我马上回来
Hold on a sec 'cause I'm going to be right back.
我需要喝点水  喝点水
I... I need some water. Some water.
好吧  我马上...就稍等一会
Okay? So, I'll... just... hold on.
没关系  我就继续练练嗓子吧
No worries. I'll just keep my vocal chords warm.
好极了
Yeah.
"他是个无关紧要的人"
"Oh, he's no one important".
"带着小不点儿汉弗莱一边玩去"
"Just take little coyote Humphrey and run along."
小不点儿
Coyote.
-小白脸呢  -他叫卡斯
- Where's Barf? - It's Garth.
我们中场休息一下
And we're just taking a little break.
休息一下吗
A break?
怎么啦  很奇怪吗
What? Is that so strange?
不不不  你开什么玩笑
No. No, no, no, no. Are you kidding?
我总喜欢狼嚎间休息个十分钟
I always like to take a break 10 minutes into a howl.
我的确要休息一下
Well, I do.
你的狼嚎伙伴  他不是...  身大无脑
Your howling partner, he's not a...he's not a stud.
不是身大无脑  虽很像"身大无脑"
Not a stud but, like, it's like "stud"
但...是个无用鬼  无用鬼  是吧
but...a dud. A dud. That's it. Isn't he?
不是
No.
他不是无用鬼
He is not a dud.
实际上  汉弗莱  你会很惊奇地
In fact, Humphrey, you'd be surprised
发现他很...强壮
to find that he is...strong!
没错  没错  强壮  他很...
Yes. Yes! Strong! And he's... He's...
-骄傲  -对  对
-Proud! -Yes! Yes.
骄傲  他很...那词怎么说来着
Proud. And he's... What's the word I'm looking for?
是阿尔法中的阿尔法
An Alpha's Alpha.
对  他是阿尔法中的阿尔法
That is right! He is an Alpha's Alpha.
你真让我生气
You make me so mad!
嘿  我刚才开玩笑的
Hey, I was just kidding.
你很可爱
You're kind of cute.
真的吗  你认为...哇  我  可爱
Really? You think... So, wow. Okay. Cute. Yeah.
那个...听着  首先  谢谢夸奖
That's...look...Thank you, first of all,
可是你指的"可爱"是
but do you mean "Cute" in,
有点硬汉的  帅帅的"可爱"吗
like, a rugged, kind of handsomely ''Cute''?
屁股上又来一下
Again with the butt.
这些蚊子真是无法无天
These mosquitoes are out of control.
我们火星上见
I'll meet you on Mars,
就在我喝下银河系后
right after I eat the Milky Way.
听起来不错
That sounds good.
留一些给我
Save some for me.
把他们装起来  我们去爱德华州
Bag them up, boys. We're going to Idaho.
遵命  头儿
You got it, chief.
好  就这样  小心那里
Okay. There we go. Watch out there.
凯特?
Kate?
多谢参观贾斯珀国家公园
我在哪儿
Where am I?
汉弗莱吗
Humphrey?
是你吗
Is that you?
凯特  我们这是在哪儿
Kate! Where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们可能已经死了
Maybe we're dead.
没有  绝对没死
Nope. Definitely not dead.
最起码他们有水让我们喝
At least they left us some water.
你有水喝吗
You got water?
不对  绝对不是水
Nope. Definitely not water.
凯特  你在干嘛呢
Kate, what are you doing?
试着逃出去
Trying to get out.
冷静一下
Calm down.
听着  他们可能要把我们送去
Listen, maybe they're taking us to
食物更充足的地方
where there's more food.
又或者我们就是食物
Or maybe we are the food.
有道理  反抗  反抗
Kate, you're right. Fight. Fight. Fight. Fight.
好了
Yeah.
可以了  放他们出来吧
All right. Set them free.
看他们跑的
Look at them go.
哇
Wow.
这里不是贾斯珀公园
This isn't Jasper.
但这里实在是帅呆了
Yeah, but it sure does... Rock!
快点  趴下
Quick, get down!
他们在干嘛呢
What are they doing?
这将是多么令人沸腾的时刻啊
What a smashingly brilliant story this is.
来自北极圈的小鹅
The golfing goose from the low
积分正遥遥领先
regions of the Arctic Circle is leading the pack.
他用错球杆了
He's using the wrong club.
能帮个忙吗  小刺们
Could you do me a favor, Needles,
请闭上你们说话的洞
and shut the hole that makes the words.
看起来  它们在玩某种诡异的游戏
Looks like they're playing some sort of weird game.
或许他们知道能让我们回家的路
Maybe they can tell us how to get home.
好主意  如果他们不知道的话
Yeah. And if they can't,
我们就吃了他们
we can eat them.
没错  跟我走
Yeah. Follow my lead.
我就在你身后
Yeah, I'm right behind you.
这杆是我的了
Now you will see, this shot is mine.
帅呆了  漂亮一击
Splendid! Wonderful hit, sir.
马上就好
Just a minute!
过程纠结了点  不过跑得不错
It's ugly, but a good runner.
你看见了吗  看见了吗
Did you see that? Did you see that?
这鸟毁了你的小鸟球
I guess the birdie ruined your Birdie.
你说了小鸟球  说明你承认球进洞了
You mark it ''Birdie'' because it would have gone in.
理论上来说  是可能会进
Technically, sir, it might have gone in.
我的球被那只蠢鸟给毁了
That silly bird stopped my shot from going in.
所以  就不应该再记杆了
So, I will not take an extra stroke.
快记下  是小鸟球
Mark it Birdie!
那  那算是个障碍物
Well, it... it was an obstacle.
不管谁打  都得有障碍物
And everyone has to play with the obstacles.
再说了  我们不能打假球
You know, we wouldn't want to lie.
如果你是法国人的话这压根不算假球
This is not a lie. This is not a lie if you are French.
法裔加拿大人
Well, French-Canadian. There's a slash,
不能算是法国人
a hyphen, in between there.
-我就认为是法国人  -加拿大人
- I say French. - Canadian.
-法国  -加拿大
- French. - Canadian.
-法国  -加拿大  先生
- French! - Canadian, sir.
不管怎么说  您都是个厉害的高尔夫球员
May I just say, though, that you are a wonderful golfer.
你也是个非常好的球童
And you are a very good caddie.
快跑
Take off!
帕蒂  你怎么了
Paddy, what is wrong with you?
你  你们好
Hello.
你们是  两只狼
You are two wolves.
虽然我在这还没怎么见过狼
I have not seen many wolves in these parts.
但是我不怕  不怕
But I am not afraid of wolves. No.
我爱狼
I Iike wolves.
好极了  我们就想问几个问题
Good. 'Cause we just want to ask you a few questions.
没问题  快看身后
Yes. Quick! Look behind you!
抓住他
Grab him!
你是想尝尝法国式的反抗吗
So, you want to face the French Resistance?
是法裔加拿大式
That's French-Canadian!
我的屁股  屁股  屁股
My butt! My butt! My butt!
这是个有出息的欧米加
Omegas.
这已经不能算是游戏了
This is not a game anymore!
你难道不洗脚的吗
Don't you wash your feet?
小心树杈
Look out for the trees!
小心
Watch that.
真漂亮  先生
Nice one, sir.
抓住你啦
Gotcha.
不
Oh, no.
这样会很痛的
That's got to hurt.
感觉如何  小蠢狼
How do you like it now, wolf?
一杆即中  先生
Hole in one, sir.
兄弟  我可不是那么容易对付的
You have bit of more than you can chew this time, my friend.
救命
Help!
天哪  我得找个
My goodness. I... Look out for the...
不  不  不  不
No. No. No. No. No. No.
他肯定完蛋了
He's a goner for sure.
等等  你们在看什么  看什么呢
Wait, what are you looking at? What are you looking at?
弗兰克  见到你真好
Hey, Frank.
好吧  你有什么问题
Okay. You have a question?
没错  我们现在在哪儿
Yeah. Where are we?
爱达荷
Idaho?
啥跟啥
Ida-who?
爱达荷  一个有山  有河  有湖
Oui, Idaho, land of mountains, rivers, lakes,
还有很多很多土豆的地方
and a few billion potatoes.
锯齿国家公园
Sawtooth National Wilderness.
爱达荷  我们在这里干嘛
What are we doing in Idaho?
你们被安排到这里来繁衍后代
You were relocated to repopulate.
他们希望你们大狼  能生一堆小狼
They want you big wolves to make a lot of little wolves.
听上去不错啊  公园里可不能少了狼
Sounds good to me. Park shouldn't be without some wolves.
我的意思是  对公园来说  挺好的
I mean, only for the good of the park.
所以  你们是非法同居对吧
So you two are undomesticated partners?
帕蒂  好好说话
Paddy, please. Don't be rude.
你们是男女朋友吧
So, you two are boyfriend, girlfriend?
你们合二为一了吗
You are an item?
-这个  -没有
- Well... - No.
你们这些狼  可真有趣
You wolves, you are funny.
我们必须马上回家
We have to get home now.
我不回去的话贾斯珀会有大麻烦的
There's going to be trouble if I don't get back to Jasper.
好吧  好吧  你有点神经质了
Right. All right. You're freaking out.
我没发疯  只是我不得不回去
I'm not freaking out. I just have to get home.
-是因为那小白脸吗  -他叫卡斯
- Is this about Barf? - It's Garth.
再说了这是关乎责任的问题
And it's about responsibilities.
我也不指望你能懂
So, I don't expect you to understand.
能请你帮个忙吗
Can you help me?
我需要马上回家
I need to get home fast.
好吧  速速小姐
All right, Miss Fast.
你温馨的家在哪儿
Where is home sweet home?
加拿大的贾斯珀公园
Jasper Park, Canada.
贾斯珀公园  开玩笑啊
Jasper park? Get out of here.
我们最喜欢贾斯珀公园了
We love Jasper Park!
没错  没错  我们去那儿旅游好多次了
Yes, yes. We've toured it many times.
拜托  帕蒂  我们去那旅游很多次了
Paddy, please. We've toured it many times.
我和一只从那儿过来的尖嘴鸭约会过一次
I dated a pintail from Jasper once.
她一直呱呱地叫个不停  我都要疯了
She never stopped quacking. Drove me nuts.
你受不了的话正好给我
Drove her right to me.
注定的  注定的
Bound to happen. Bound to happen.
那你能帮我回家了
So, you can help me, then, get home.
我们好久没上贾斯珀那儿玩了
We haven't played Jasper in quite a while.
听上去会是个不错的主意
I think it would be a smashing idea.
确实如此  我会帮助你们的
This is true. So, of course I will help.
我喜欢你俩  你们是我的开心果
I like you two. You make me laugh.
再说了  我还欠你们一个人情
And you didn't eat me,
因为你们没有吃我
so I owe you favor.
她去哪儿了
Where did she go?
那正是我要问的问题
Maybe I should ask you.
你知道这不是我的风格
You know that's not my style.
我的部下  小能  了解你的风格
My wolf, Can-do, knows your style.
我就想说一件事
I just want to say one thing.
如果你的手下胆敢伤害我女儿
If any of you wolves have hurt my daughter,
我会亲自挖出你的眼睛
I will personally rip out
塞进你的喉咙
your eyes and shove them down your throat
让你亲眼看到我是如何撕裂你的身体的
so you can see my claws tear your carcass open!
妈妈
Mom?
宝贝  妈妈在怒火中  一会儿再说
Not now, dear. Mommy's in a rage.
既然凯特放了卡斯飞机
Well, since Kate stood up Garth,
我可以在她回来之前带卡斯到处看看
I could show him around until she gets back.
我不会说她放了我飞机
I wouldn't say ''Stood up.''
卡斯
Garth!
听起来不错
Sounds good to me.
那来吧  卡斯
Well, come on, Garth.
很温柔吧  从我这儿继承的
Isn't that sweet? She gets it from me.
满月是最后时限
I'll give her till the full moon.
今天天气特别好
It is beautiful out there.
都有去田地里挖土豆的冲动了
Almost makes you want to hit the potato patch.
如果你还没出门的话就快行动吧
If you haven't already hit the outdoors, get on out your door.
今天的天气是...
The weather today is...
你们回家的车
Your ride home.
快  进去
Quick! Get in!
搞什么  一天被关在箱子里两回
What? Boxed up twice in one day.
什么倒霉运啊
What are the odds?
-躲起来  -快
- Hide! - Hide!
那是斯卡蔻丝夫妇
That right there is Garn and Debbie Theocarcus.
你们运气不错
Lucky for you, they travel
他们每年都会先去锯齿再去贾斯珀
every year to Jasper right after Sawtooth.
天气真好  老婆大人气色也非常不错
The day's looking pretty, and so is my woman.
这是那首让我们相遇的歌
This is the song we met to.
来  亲爱的  我们来跳舞吧
Come here, you. Let's dance.
-钻进来  -快
- Down here. - Hurry.
他曾经摩托车队的  她是图书管理员
Now, he was in a motorcycle gang, and she was a librarian.
所谓异性相吸
And opposites attract, if you will.
没错  不过这次是因为书店也贩卖啤酒
Exactly. In this case, it was a bookstore that also sold beer.
他们就这么相遇了
So, they met.
快  我们得进车里了
Come on. We have to get in.
棒极了
All right. Here we go.
你就是我的白马王子
You're just a dream.
我跳起来像个小兔子  对吧  亲爱的
I'm like a little bunny. Aren't I, dear?
我爱你  黛比
I love you, Deb.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
快进去  快
Get inside now. Get inside. Quick.
哎  又要回箱子里了
Well, back in a box.
你俩一路顺风
Good luck, you two!
我们会在天上照看你们的
We will be watching out for you from above!
好吧  我会看着你们的
Well, I'll be watching out for you.
他会在一旁喘气
He will be breathing heavily.
如果无从选择  我们会为了溪谷而战斗
If we have to, we'll fight for the valley.
汉弗莱
Humphrey?
为什么要叫兔粑粑山
So, why is this called Rabbit Poo Mountain?
因为兔子爱在这个地方拉屎
Because this is where rabbits like to poo.
开个玩笑啦
I was just kidding.
我懂了  你是负责搞笑的欧米加
I get it. You're a funny Omega.
好吧  快逗我笑
Okay. Make me laugh.
我是谁
What am I?
这难到我了
You got me.
是个翻不过身来的海龟
It's a turtle that fell and can't get up.
挺像的
That's pretty good.
那这又是什么呢
Okay. What's this?
是个在路上被压死的海龟
It's turtle road kill.
你还能扮什么
What else can you do?
我只会扮海龟
I just do turtles.
好了  该到我了
Okay, it's my turn.
你想看看阿尔法会做什么吗
You want to see something an Alpha can do?
我妈会同意吗
Would my mother approve?
当然
Of course.
那好吧
Well, okay then.
继续找  我们必须在明天晚上之前找到她
Keep searching. We must find her before tomorrow night.
温斯顿
Winston?
别担心  伊夫
Don't worry, Eve.
她是我训练过得最好的阿尔法
She's the finest Alpha I've trained.
我没担心  温斯顿
I'm not, Winston.
她也是我训练过得最好的阿尔法
She's also the finest Alpha I've ever trained.
车停了
We stopped.
-你怎么了  -我要小解
- What's wrong with you? - I have to go.
你不能离开  就不能多忍一下吗
You can't leave. Can't you hold it?
不  我做不到
No! I can't.
好吧  试过盘腿了吗
Well, did you try crossing your legs?
-试过了  -那屏住呼吸呢
-Yes! - Holding your breath?
试过了  我屏得差点要晕过去了
Yes! I almost passed out.
-闭上眼睛  -里面还是外面  我不行了
- Closing your eyes and... - In or out, I am going.
你就不能快点吗
Would you hurry?
我有压力的时候解不出来
I can't go when I feel pressured.
速度啊
Go!
他到底在干吗
What is he doing?
这包装居然是防狼的
The packaging's wolf-proof.
他跑哪儿去了
Where is he?
快过来  汉弗莱
Come on, Humphrey.
有恶狼
It's a rabid wolf!
马克斯  把枪拿出来
Max, bring that gun!
我送你一程  恶狼  有遗言吗
This is it for you, wolf. Any last wishes?
马克斯  他们跑了
Max, they're getting away!
有我在  他们跑不了
Not if I can help it.
-不  -我们被困住了
- No! - We're trapped.
逮着你俩了
I got you both now.
快打他们
Shoot them!
打得真"好"啊  马克斯
Nicely done, Max.
好吧  我饿昏了头
Okay. Thinking with my belly instead of my head,
我现在知道那不是个好主意
not a good idea. I get it.
我建议咱可以弄个舒服的窝
I say we build a comfy den...
-我要回家  -好吧
- I'm going home. - Great.
我知道你要回家  可这在下雨啊
You're going home, and it's raining.
我不会停下来的
I'm not stopping.
雨啊  雨啊  快停吧
Rain, rain, go away.
快停吧  雨啊  没人希望你下
Get out of here, rain no one wants you around
你在搞什么
What are you doing?
这  这是求雨舞  为了让雨停下来的舞
It's... It's a rain dance, to stop it from raining.
因为你太湿了  毁了我们的一天
'Cause you're wet and you really are going to ruin our day
汉弗莱  求雨舞是求下雨的
Humphrey, rain dances make it rain.
好吧  那我反着跳
Right! Well, I'll just do it backwards.
真有效果唉
That actually worked.
凯特
Kate?
哎  估计那不是什么好点子
That's not a good idea.
等等我  凯特
Hold on, Kate!
不
No!
坚持住  凯特  我来了
Hold on, Kate! I'm coming!
让我想想  想想
Let me think. Let me think.
汉弗莱
Humphrey!
别怕  凯特  刚那是计划的一部分
Don't worry, Kate. It's all part of my plan.
我看出来了
I can see that.
凯特  凯特  抓住我的尾巴
Kate. Kate! Grab my tail.
抓住你什么
Grab your what?
用你那阿尔法的嘴咬住...
Take those Alpha jaws and grab...
我的尾巴啊  尾巴
My tail. My tail.
凯特  摆起来  转圈摆
Kate, wiggle. Wiggle around.
好痒啊  我的尾巴好痛
That tickles. My tail hurts!
谁会知道我那儿怕痒呢
Who knew I was ticklish there?
我坚持不住了
I can't take any more.
不
No.
天哪  汉弗莱  汉弗莱
My gosh. Humphrey! Humphrey!
你的尾巴  天哪  都是我的错
Your tail. I'm so sorry.
我的尾巴还在
My tail's actually fine,
我已经检查过啦
last time I checked.
来吧  我们找个地方躲雨吧
Come on. Let's get out of the rain.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
头  我们已经搜寻完整个领地了
Sir, we've searched the entire territory.
还是没有发现凯特的踪影
Still no sign of Kate.
头
Sir?
我们必须保卫我们的领地
We must defend our territory.
球来啦
Fore!
看  看  看  这里都发生什么了
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
好像来的不是时候哦
I say, we've caught them at quite the bad time.
不对  我们来的正是时候
No, I'd say we caught them at a good time.
确实如此  先生
Indeed, sir. Indeed.
你俩在这儿干吗
What are you doing here?
问题应该是  你俩在这儿干吗
No, the question is what are you doing here?
我可是给了你俩  头等舱的票子啊
I give you a first class ticket home...
可是直达的唉
It's a straight shot right to the pin.
-你们却不坐了吗  -是的
- And you blow it? - Yep.
就为了个杯形蛋糕
Over a cupcake.
真荒谬  "杯形蛋糕"
Ridiculous dessert. ''A cupcake.''
事实上  它们的确挺好吃的
Actually, they're quite delicious.
肯定有其他去贾斯珀的办法
There has to be another way for us to get to Jasper.
其他办法  其他办法吗
Another way? Another way?
其他办法  当我是旅游代理啊
Always another way. What am I, a travel agent?
别这样  你在耍我吗
Come on. What, are you kidding me?
一个像你这样成功的运动员
A great sportsman like yourself
总知道很多赢得比赛的方法
always knows a few ways to win the game.
或许可以乘火车
Well, there could be a train.
事实上  确实有趟火车  叫做加拿大特快
Actually, there is a train. It's the Canadian Express and...
拜托  帕蒂  那叫加拿大特快
Paddy, please. It's called the Canadian Express...
没错  直达贾斯珀公园
Yes, and it shoots right by Jasper Park.
直达贾斯珀公园
Right by Jasper Park.
-如果能赶上的话  -马上就能到家了
- If you can catch it... - You'll be home in no time.
马上  非常快
No time. Very fast.
太棒了  我们在哪儿上车呢
Great. So where do we board?
在哪儿上车呢
Where do you board?
看这个
Watch this.
在山的另外一边
On the other side of that mountain.
拜托  帕蒂
Paddy, please.
我们走吧
Come on!
是我没管好嘴巴  但能再容许我说句
Let it slip, but may I say,
刚刚那球真是棒极了
that was a stupendous shot.
批准了  那球真的很棒  不是吗
You may, and it was pretty good, wasn't it?
确实  先生
Indeed, sir. Indeed.
两人份晚餐
Dinner for two.
这是我在盯梢猎物时新学会的动作
It's a new move I've been working on for stalking prey.
帅呆了
You're good.
谢谢  该你了
Thanks. Now you try.
不  我
No. I...
我不太会捕猎
I'm not much of a hunter.
来吧  你会做得很好的
Come on. You'll do great.
就跟着我做
Just do what I do.
好吧
Okay.
预备
Ready?
-一  -一
- One. - One.
-二  -二
- Two. - Two.
三
Three!
莉莉
Lilly!
Lilly?
是个海龟  没错吧
A turtle, right?
我都告诉过你了  我不会捕猎
I told you, I don't hunt.
也许这样可以帮你
Maybe this will help.
哇哦
Wow.
"哇哦"什么
''Wow'' what?
你的眼睛好漂亮
Your eyes. They're beautiful.
来吧  咱再试一次
Come on. Let's try again.
-这儿真美  -是啊
- It sure is pretty out there. - Yeah.
-来比比谁先跑到山顶吧  -接受挑战
- I'll race you to the top. - You're on.
认输吧  汉弗莱  你永远也追不上我的
Give it up, Humphrey! You'll never beat me.
汉弗莱
Humphrey?
欧米加胜一分  阿尔法零分
Omega one, Alpha zero!
好了  好了
Okay! Okay!
够了够了  停下快停下
Enough, enough! Stop! Stop!
我知道了  知道了  知道了
I get it. I get it. I get it.
作为一个女生  我投的怎么样啊
How's that for a girl's throw?
很有意思
Very funny.
看看你玩的多开心呀
Well, look who's having fun.
你知道  我应该去看看火车什么时候来
You know, I should go check on the train.
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait!
等等我  等等
Wait, wait.
嗨  你好啊
Hi, there.
你是什么呀
What are you?
好吧  我是匹狼
Well, I'm a wolf.
我从没见过狼  你长得真奇怪
I've never seen a wolf. You are really strange.
我真的很奇怪吗
Am I now?
你长得太奇怪啦
You're totally weird.
我要抓住你
I'm going to get you!
好了  小心  小心
No. Look out! Look out!
好吧  你自找的啊
Okay, you asked for it.
不哭不哭不哭  没事的  没事的
No, no, no. It's okay. It's okay.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
不是吧
Oh, poo.
疯...
Mad...
疯熊
Mad bear.
凯特  准备好雪球  疯熊来袭
Kate! Get the snowballs ready! Mad bear on the attack!
加拿大特快  汉弗莱  火车来了
The Canadian Express! Humphrey, the train is coming!
凯特
Kate!
汉弗莱
Humphrey?
你怎么啦
What's wrong with you?
看那儿
That!
别动  我们可以对付
Don't move. We can handle this.
真的吗
We can?
好吧  我们有麻烦了
Okay, we're in trouble.
伙计们  你们喜欢听笑话吗  很好
Guys. You guys like jokes? Good.
那听着  两只熊正在吃一个笨蛋
So, okay. So two bears are eating a clown,
其中一只熊说
and one of the bears says,
"你不觉得这个味道很怪吗"
"Does this taste funny to you?"
你说句"切"就行了啊
A simple "boo" would have sufficed.
老天啊
Man.
看招  再来  再来
Watch this. One more. One more.
起来  凯特  快起来
Get up. Kate, get up.
他俩上哪儿去啦
Where are those two?
他俩怎么总把事情搞得这么复杂呢
Why must they make this so difficult?
用"难伺候的一对"来形容
I believe the term is
最贴切不过了  先生
"high maintenance couple", sir.
前有利爪后有悬崖  这可不妙啊
Stuck between the cliffs and the claws. This isn't good.
真希望你能用开玩笑摆脱这个困境
Good luck joking your way out of this one.
你叫什么  先生
What's your name, sir?
你叫咆哮  好吧
Growl. All right.
你想要拥抱一下吗
Do you need a hug?
我们为什么不谈谈呢  我们谈谈好吗
Why don't we talk? Can we just talk?
真是愉快的谈话
Good talk!
嗨  要我载你一程吗
Hey, need a ride?
跳过来  相信我
Jump! Trust me!
我说吧  你可以相信我的
I told you, you could trust me.
向左
Hang a left!
向右
Go right!
你干嘛这样看着我
Why are you looking at me like that?
难以置信  他俩竟然错过火车了
Unbelievable. They have missed the train.
看来没有
Or not.
我知道  不是很好听  对吧
I know. It's not very good, is it?
好吧
Well...
你用雪球那招太棒啦
That was so awesome. You with the snowballs.
还有你和那只小熊打雪仗
And you with that little
真是太可爱啦
bear in that snowball fight. It was so cute.
还有你用木头滑下时
But then you with the log!
当时你脸上的表情真是太精彩了
The look on your face was so good.
然后我们...
And then we...
你知道吗  我们真是很好的组合
You know, we make a pretty good team.
凯特和汉弗莱  世界探险家  你觉得怎样
Kate and Humphrey, world adventurers! What do you think?
我觉得你疯了
I think you're crazy.
你觉得我...
You think I'm...
不  我告诉你
No, I'm telling you,
我们可要去干一番大事业
we're onto something here.
和我待在一起吧  小家伙
Stick with me, pup.
我们要周游世界
We'll go places.
好啊  我会记在心里的
Well, I'll keep that in mind.
好了  深呼吸
All right. Take a deep breath.
从这儿嚎叫出来
Howl from right here.
我会和你一起嚎叫的
And I'll join in.
汉弗莱
Humphrey,
你在干嘛呢
what are you doing?
抱歉  只是这月亮
I'm sorry. The moon,
此时此刻  我只是想
the moment. I just thought...
来吧  凯特  和我一起对月长嚎吧
Come on, Kate. Howl at the moon with me.
北太平洋
看吧  你唱的太棒了
See? That's so good.
不好  你最好快离开
No. You better go.
但没人知道啊
But no one has to know.
求你了  现在快离开
Please. Go, now.
不好
No.
爸爸
Dad.
和欧米加一起嚎叫  我们这么低贱吗
Howling with an Omega, are we?
-我只是...  -和其他人一起去
- I was just... - Get with the others.
发生什么事情了
What's going on?
我们要去占领山谷  夺回我们的驯鹿
We're going to take the valley, and our caribou.
-父亲  -莉莉  出什么事了
- Dad! - Lilly, what's wrong?
东部狼群  它们来了
The Eastern Wolves. They're coming!
来吧
Come on!
只管去做  她刚和你一起对月嚎叫了
Just do it. She howled at the moon with you.
那纯粹是个偶然
That was just the moment.
你好呀  毛茸茸的朋友
Bonjour, my furry friend.
什么
What?
你们疯了吗
Are you guys crazy?
这可要讨论决定
That's up for debate.
那位年轻的女士呢
And where is... Mademoiselle.
她在睡觉  小声点
She's sleeping, so be quiet.
遵命  小声点
Yes. Quiet.
你们这些家伙上这儿来干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
确保你们没有忘记行驶路线
Making sure that you don't forget the run of the course.
贾斯珀公园  几英里后就到了
Jasper Park, it is a few miles up.
可不要错过了
Do not miss it.
贾斯珀  几英里后  知道了
Jasper, few miles, got it.
很好
Good.
我不得不说
I've got to say, your
你女朋友睡觉的时候真漂亮
girlfriend looks quite pretty when she sleeps.
她不是我的女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
那你可得好好努力了
You should work on that.
今天是满月  温斯顿
It's the full moon, Winston.
我看得见  托尼
I can see that, Tony.
我也不想把事情变成这样
I didn't want it to come to this.
但结果还是这样了
But here we are.
停止发疯  有机生活
Stop the insanity! Go organic!
加拿大贾斯珀国家公园
凯特
Kate.
凯特  醒醒  快醒醒
Kate, wake up. Wake up.
汉弗莱  我们到哪儿了
Humphrey? Where are we?
我们...  我们到了贾斯珀
We're... We're in Jasper.
我们到家了
We're home.
是啊  到家了
Yup. We're home.
-有些事...  -有些事...
- There's something... - There's something...
你先请
Please, you first.
汉弗莱  我想告诉你
Humphrey, I just wanted to tell you,
过去的这些天  挺有趣的
these past couple of days, they've been, kind of, fun.
你也是挺有趣的
You've been, kind of, fun.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
好吧  那  那太棒了
Well, that's... That's great.
我告诉过你  我们是很好的组合
I told you, we make a pretty good team.
是啊
We do.
好吧
Okay. Well.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
不要告诉我你又要上厕所了
Don't tell me. You have to go to the bathroom again.
为什么  你看到辆卡车停下来了吗
Why, do you see a truck stop?
我就是想告诉你  我...  我...
I just wanted to tell you I... I...
-我...  我就是想告诉你  -不好
- I... I just wanted to tell you... - No.
我...  我爱...
I... I love...
哎
Oh, geez.
我要求的只是遵照传统  联合部落
All I asked was for you to follow our customs, unite the packs.
但是相反  你女儿却逃跑了
But, no. Your daughter had to up and run away.
我没有逃跑
I didn't run away.
凯特
Kate!
她回来了
She's back!
-我们担心死了  -你上哪儿去了
- We were so worried. - Where have you been?
-爱达荷州  -爱达荷州吗
- In Idaho. - Idaho?
你去爱达荷州干什么
What were you doing in Idaho?
我们被人类带到了另外一个公园
We were taken by humans to another park.
我们本应该去繁殖后代的
We were supposed to repopulate.
不不不  妈妈  我们没有繁殖后代
No, no, no. Mom. We didn't repopulate.
实际上还是汉弗莱帮我回家的
Humphrey actually helped me get home.
真是个好男孩
What a nice boy.
-我回来...  -你是回来和卡斯结婚的
- I came back... - You came back to marry Garth.
是的
Yes.
还有联合部落
And unite the packs!
对部落好  让肚子饱
Good for the pack, good for the belly.
结婚吗  你要结婚了吗
Marry? You're getting married?
是的  这不是很好吗
Yes. Isn't it great?
捕食时不会再有争斗了
No more fighting during hunts.
晚餐时不用再吃骨头肉屑了
No more scraps and bones at dinnertime.
我们将会联合部落
We're going to unite the packs.
欢迎回来  汉弗莱
Welcome back, Humphrey.
把她带回家  真是好样的
Good job bringing her home.
好多人啊
Wow. It's a big crowd.
是啊  好日子嘛
Yeah. Good times.
我听说你和卡斯相处了一段时间
So I heard you and Garth spent some time together.
莉莉
Lilly.
抱歉
Sorry.
我想他肯定是个结婚的好对象
I'm sure he's perfect marrying material.
是啊  如果你喜欢高大
Well, if you like that sort of thing, big,
强壮  完美型的
brawny, and perfect.
莉莉  你把毛向后梳了
Lilly, you're wearing your fur back.
抱歉  我知道了
Sorry. I know.
但是我很喜欢啊
But, I liked it.
正中旗杆
Right on the pin.
马塞尔  帕蒂
Marcel! Paddy!
当拥抱的时候
When it comes to hugs,
我们都成了法国人  对吧  帕蒂
we are all French, Paddy?
好吧  我是英国人  所以我们不拥抱
Well, I'm English, so we don't hug!
但头一次  我要说这个拥抱很不错
But for a first, I'd say that was a good one.
见到你俩我真是太开心了
I'm so happy to see you two.
我们飞过来确认你们到家了
We flew in to see that you made it home.
然后我们发现了什么
And what do we find?
-你要结婚了  -你要结婚了
- You're getting married! - You're getting married!
是啊  我要结婚了
Yeah. I'm getting married.
-谁告诉你们的  -我
- Who told you? - I did.
汉弗莱
Humphrey.
我们应该走了
We should be going.
是的  是的
Yes, yes.
不好意思  一只跳蚤
Excuse me. A flea.
还有给你婚礼的一点小心意
And a little something for your big day.
谢谢
Thank you.
只是想来跟你道别
Just wanted to say good-bye.
道别
Good-bye?
是啊  我想出去旅行一下
Yeah. I'm thinking about doing a little traveling,
你知道  看看火车会把我带到哪儿
you know, seeing where the train takes me.
也许我还会去拜访我们的狗熊朋友
And maybe I'll visit our friends the bears.
老伙计们  看看他们过得怎么样
Our old buddies, see how they're doing.
我会向他们转达你的问候
I'll tell them you said hi.
等等  你要离开贾斯珀了吗
Wait. But you're leaving Jasper?
是的  你知道  孤独的狼都这样嘛
Yeah. You know, it's a lone wolf thing.
我了解的汉弗莱  是个风趣的欧米加
I know Humphrey, the fun-loving Omega,
而不是一匹孤独的狼
not Humphrey, the lone wolf.
那我就是匹风趣的孤独的狼
So I'll be a fun-loving lone wolf.
我知道的
I don't doubt that.
你知道吗  马塞尔  我一向坚守传统
You know, Marcel, I am a stickler for tradition,
但是这个我就不能理解了
but this one, I just don't understand.
这些狼啊  可真难理解
These wolves are mysterious creatures.
托尼
Tony.
那么...
So...
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
是的
Yes.
很好
Good.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
当然
You bet.
我这边可没问题
No problems on this end.
准备好开始开始开始啦
Ready to go, go, go.
那么你希望谁先开始
So, you want to start this thing or me?
我们一起开始
We'll start together.
一起开始  好啊
Start together. Yeah.
怎么啦
So, what's happening?
他们在相互嗅对方的气味
They're accepting each other's scent.
现在  轻轻的互咬耳朵
And now, the nibble on the ears.
你们觉得我能做到吗
Do you think I can make it?
当然  先生  你顺着轨道跑
Yes, sir, and just as you hit the tracks,
你会看到一截开着的火车车厢
you should see an open train car.
小心卡车停靠  熊
Well, avoid truck stops, bears,
还有那个可怕的甜点  叫什么来着
and that hideous dessert. What is it called?
-杯形蛋糕  先生  -是的  杯形蛋糕
- Cupcakes, sir. - Yes. Cupcakes.
我会注意的  多谢  伙计们
I will. Thanks, guys.
你知道吗  你不该对杯形蛋糕那么苛刻
You know, you shouldn't be so judgmental about cupcakes.
它们真的很美味
They really are quite delicious.
再好吃又如何
I wouldn't know.
最后  他们要相互摩擦鼻子
And finally, they will rub noses
那就代表他们是夫妻了
to symbolize that they are mates!
凯特  你怎么啦
Kate, what are you doing?
我...
I...
我做不到
I can't.
你做不到吗
You can't!
我的意思是  你做不到
I mean, you can't?
这是怎么回事  温斯顿
What is this, Winston?
她为什么不能嫁给卡斯
Why can't she marry Garth?
安静点
Quiet.
凯特  凯特  你为什么不能嫁给卡斯
Kate, Kate. Why can't you marry Garth?
因为我...
Because I...
因为我爱上了一个欧米加
I fell in love with an Omega.
一个欧米加吗
An Omega?
汉弗莱吗  那个狡猾的家伙
Humphrey? That sly dog!
阿尔法爱上欧米加  那可是违反部落规定的
An Alpha in love with an Omega. That's against pack law.
爸爸
Dad.
我也爱上了一个欧米加
I also am in love with an Omega.
什么
What?
你都对我儿子做了些什么  温斯顿
What have you done to my son, Winston?
欧米加和阿尔法  阿尔法和欧米加
An Omega and an Alpha? An Alpha and an Omega?
伊夫  帮帮我
Eve, help me out.
真是太疯狂了  这可不符合传统
This is madness. This isn't our custom.
我们可不会这么做  占领山谷
This isn't our way. Take the valley!
我最喜欢婚礼了
I just love weddings!
鹿群大狂奔  鹿群大狂奔
Stampede! Stampede!
大家快跑  快跑
Everyone, run! Run!
到山谷的两边去
To the sides of the valley!
我背上那块该死的骨头又僵了
It's that darn disk in my back.
快跑
Come on!
不好  他们被困住了
No! They're trapped!
汉弗莱
Humphrey!
凯特
Kate!
我们必须去帮他们
We have to help them!
快看
Look!
跑快点  托尼  再快点
Faster, Tony! Faster!
向左
Go left!
右翻转
Roll right!
你学得真快啊
You're getting good at this.
名师出高徒嘛
I had a good teacher.
离他们太远了  我们赶不到的
They're too far ahead. We'll never make it.
抓紧了
Hold on.
看
Look!
世界探险者
World adventurers.
我说过我们是很好的组合嘛
I told you we'd make a good team.
你说的吗  我记得是我说的
Did you say that? I thought I said that.
凯特
Kate!
凯特  凯特
Kate. Kate.
求你了  凯特
Please, Kate.
求你了  你不能这么做
Please, you can't do this.
我爱你
I love you.
凯特
Kate!
汉弗莱
Humphrey?
我还以为我失去你了
I thought I'd lost you.
大家都在看着我们吗
Is everyone staring at us?
好吧  没有  没有  不是所有人
Well, no, not... Not every...
好吧  是的  现在都在看了
Well, yeah. Now they are.
见鬼  因为有些事我要告诉你
Darn. 'Cause I wanted to tell you something.
什么
What?
真的吗
Really?
好吧  我也有些事要告诉你
Okay. Well, I wanted to tell you something, too.
也许这并没有什么问题
Maybe this can work.
好吧
All right.
卡斯
Garth!
托尼  你说我们两匹老狼
Tony, what do two old wolves do
退休了后能干什么
after they retire?
先生们  请允许我给你们介绍高尔夫
Gentlemen, may I introduce you to golf?
球来了
Fore!
真不错
Oh, that's good.
来吧  宝贝  让我们给他们做个示范
Come on, honey. Let's show 'em how it's done.
准备好摇摆尾巴了吗
You ready to shake your tail?
那嚎叫真是美妙动听极了
Now that's a howl.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
当然准备好了
Oh. Ready.